Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
- Video Cassettes (VC), 1979-2006; VII.
  - Individuals, February 28, 1992 - August 29, 2001; 6.
    Lieberman, Senator Joseph. Senator and Vice Presidential candidate, Democratic Party, general election 2000. Campaign speech with foreign policy as the subject, Nov.3, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VI.5 See also, UPG.RG.55 News Clippings, 2000.
    McWhinney, Dr. Norman N. Retirement, December, 1995. VC VI.2
    O'Connor, J. Dennis Installation as 16th Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, Carnegie Music Hall, Pittsburgh, PA., February 28, 1992. VC VI.3
    Rossetti, Dr. Guy, Guy Rossetti Memorial Commemoration, 1/25/99. [marked "Master" tape] VC VI.4 See also: UPG.RG.60.DVD.24.A.8 Spector, Arlen, US Senator (R-Pa) Town Meeting, August 29, 2001. UPG Campus, Ferguson Theater VC VI.6
    - Individuals, February 28, 1992 - August 29, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 4)
  - Performing Arts, April 6-8, 1979 - April 1-3, 2004; 7.
    Andes Manta [Andes Folk Music ensemble]. Ferguson Theater. Oct. 27, 1999. VC VII.8 Andes Manta, A Concert of Andean Music. September 19, 2002. Ferguson Theatre. (VC II.8a). [For program, see UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous.)]
    Capitol Steps. Performance 4/1/04 UPG Chambers Hall Gymnasium. Part of UPG 40th Anniversary (2003) celebration. Proceeds to UPG President's Scholarship Fund. VC VII.25 See also: UPG.RG.27 News Releases. News Release 2/16/04; UPG.RG.00 Ser.: Anniversaries. 40th, 2003; UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG President's Scholarship Fund. [n.b.: There are problems with the sound on this videocassette.]
    Grupo Folklorico de Oaxaca. September 20, 1999. VC VII.5 (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27, news release, September 1, 1999. Also see, RG52 Subject Files--Rossetti House Programming.)
    Indian Classical Music Concert. March 31, 1999. VC VII.4 Artists: Nandkishore Muley playing the santoor, known as "a hundred stringed lute" and Ramdas Palsule playing the tabla. (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27, News Release, March 19, 1999.)
    Indian Classical Music Concert. April 5, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VII.11 Featuring: Vishwa Mohan Bhatt, a 1994 Grammy Award winner performing on a modified Western acoustic guitar made by changing the main strings and adding a number of "sympathetic strings"; and Singh Mamadhari, an accomplished percussionist playing a pair of drums called "tabla".
    Indian Classical Music Concert, March 29, 2001. VC VII.12 Artists: Tejendra Majumdar on the sarod, a string instrument and Subhankar Banerjee, a percussionist on the tabla. (For news release, see UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases, Mar. 19, 2001; for video cassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Video Cassettes--VC VII.12; for photos, see RG60 Visual Images--Prints--Indian Classical Music Concert, 3/29/01).
    Indian Classical Music Concert, Oct. 22, 2002. VC VII.17 Artists: Purbayan Chatterjee on the sitar; Abhijit Banerjee on the tabla. [For news release, see UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases, Oct. 10, 2002, for video cassette, see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Videocassettes VC VII.17; for programs, see UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous); for sound Recording, see UPG.RG.62 Cassette C.12]
    Indian Classical Music Concert, Oct. 21, 2003. Ferguson Theater. VC VII.20 Artists: Ken Zuckerman, an American who directs the Ali Akbar College in Basel, Switzerland, and Aninda Chatterjee, and eminent tabla player from India. Lowen, Sharon
    Performance of Odissi, one of the major classical dance forms of India. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Smith Hall Auditorium, November 4, 1992. (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27, news release, October 22,1992.) VC VII.1
    Native American Hoop Dancer, Lisa Odjig. Oct. 28, 2003. Ferguson Theater. VC VII.21
    Palekar, Priya. VC VII.14 The International Club of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg presents "An Evening of Arias and Songs", soprano, Priya Palekar accompanied by Sean Kelly on the piano. Ferguson Theatre. Wednesday, April 10, 2002 at 7:30 p.m. (for sound cassette, see UPG.RG.61.C.9; for programs, see UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous.)
    Pampa Fusion [a Pittsburgh based ensemble of musicians from Argentina, Brazil and Chile performing folkloric Latin American music, combining classical and typical traditional musical instruments]. VC II.9 Ferguson Theater, Feb. 29, 2000. For news release, see UPG.RG.27 Ser. News Releases, 2/21/00.
    Pitt-Greensburg Drama Club [UPG Players as Pitt-Greensburg Drama Club]
    1979, Apr. 6-8. "Inherit the Wind" by Robert Lee. 1 videocassette. VC VII.16.1
    1980, Mar. 28-30. "Tragedy of Ragweed Cowboy Joe" by I.E. Clark. VC VII.16.2 1 videocassette.
    1981, April 10-12. "The Three Penny Opera" by Berthold Brecht. VC VII.16.3 2 videocassettes.
    Reddy, Dr. Kamala. Performing the Kuchipudi style of Indian classical dance. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Smith Hall, November 8, 1991. VC VII.2 (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27, news release, October 21, 1991.)
    "Requiem" by Gabriel Faure. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Chorale, Seton Hill University Choir, Members of the Westmoreland Symphony. Wednesday, April 9, 2003, 7:30 p.m., St. Joseph Chapel, Seton Hill University. With performances by the Seton Hill University Women's Chorale and Handbell Choirs. [This videocassette of the Apr. 9, 2003 performance.] VC VII.19
    The "Second Mrs. Demyan", an original play by K.C. Constantine. Sept. 24, 25, 26, 1999. Ferguson Theater. VC VII.7 Cast: Borislav "Bo" Demyan (Norman McWhinney); Denise Merski Demyan (Deborah Casciani); Joyce Merski (Valerie Drake); Alberto "Vento" Rohrbach (Christopher Scott). This was a taping of the Friday, Sept. 24, 1999 performance. (For program, news clippings, etc., see UPG.RG.25 Library Ser.: UPG Cultural Series.)
    "Student One Acts" [Student Directed One Acts]. Nov. 28-30, 2001. VC VII.24 3 videocassettes.
    "Sure Thing" by David Ives and "The Actors' Nightmare", by Christopher Durang. VC VII.13 Nov. 30, Dec. 1, 2000. Directed by Ken Lewandowski who graduated from UPG in Apr., 2000 and Laird Cain who is in his last term at UPG. (For program, see UPG.RG.52 Subject files--Programs--Miscellaeneous.)
    "Tlen-Huicani" [Mexican Folk Group]. Sept. 28, 2005, Ferguson Theater, UPG. VC VII.26 See also, UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases. News Release 9/6/05.
    Tuna, La. The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg presents La Tuna from the School of Medicine, University of Valladolis, Spain. April 14, 2003. Ferguson Theatre. VC VII.18 [For program, see UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous)]
    Tuna, La. [from the School of Medicine, University of Valladolid, Spain; performance at UPG, Jan. 15, 2004] VC VII.22
    24 Hours. AM Plus, March 21,22, 1986. 15 mini-plays written by a variety of artists and which explore the diversity of events that can happen in little more than a day in scenes that are funny and touching. Presented by Drama Club of Pitt-Greensburg under the direction of Andy Gilfillan. (For students participating in the performance and additional information, see UPG.RG.27, news releases, February 28, 1986.) VC VII.3
    UPG Chorale and Band Concert, Apr. 16, 2002. VC VII.15 (for sound cassette, see UPG.RG.61.C.10.)
    UPG Performance Collective Productions
    VC VII.23.1 a - e 2000, Mar. 25-26. "The Visit" by Friedrich Durrematt. 5 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.2 a - c 2000, Nov. 10-12. "Beyond Therapy" by Christopher Durang. 3 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.3 a - c 2001, Mar. 15-18. "The Adding Machine" by Elmer Rice. 3 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.4 a - d 2001, Sept. 13-15. "The UPG Regional One-Act Festival: The Little Red Gate" by Maureen Jenkins; "Not Lightly Chosen" by Robert C. Wittig. 4 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.5 a - e 2001, Nov. 7-10. "The Lion in Winter" by James Goldman. 5 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.6 a 2002, Mar. 20 [Dress Rehearsal?]. "Surburbia" by Eric Bogosian. 1 videocassette.
    VC VII.23.7 a - d 2002, Nov. 6-9. "Such Foolish Affected Ladies" by Moliere. 4 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.8 a - c 2003, Mar. 21-22. "Talking With" by Jane Martin. 3 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.9 a - b 2003, Nov. 20-22. R.U.R. ("Rossum's Universal Robots") by Karel Capek. 2 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.10 a - c 2004, Apr. 1-3. "Fool for Love" by Sam Shepard. 3 videocassettes.
    VC VII.23.11 2000, Spring, Fall. 45 Minute of clip of Plays of UPG Productions: "The Visit, Beyond Therapy", "The Adding Machine", "The Lion in Winter", "Surburbia", "Such Foolish Affected Ladies". 1 videocassette.
    For prints See: UPG.RG.60 Ser.: Prints. UPG Performance collective. UPG Players
    "The Proposal; The Bear" by Anton Chekhov. Nov. 20, 21, 1997. Powers Hall. VC VII.10.1 Produced by, directed by, and starring UPG Faculty Members: Sayre Greenfield, Mark McColloch, Norman McWhinney, William Pamerleau, Mary Beth Spore, Joanne Viano, Judith Vollmer. (See also UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--UPG Players and UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--UPG Players)
    The UPG Players present Two Comedies Tonight: "Overruled" by G.B. Shaw. VC VII.10.2 (Cast: Mrs. Juno, Sheila Conifer; Mr. Lunn, Bill Pamerleau; Mrs. Lunn, Jennifer Fetter; Mr. Juno, Rick Sparks; directed by Sheila Conifer) and "Mixed Doubles" by G. Feydeau (Cast: Albert, Brandi Darr; Philomele, Liz Marciniak; Pompe Nicole, Chris Lacey; Bordeleau, Mark McColloch; Venus, Mary Beth Spore; Aphrodite, Tracey Douthett; directed by Joanne Viano). March 30 & 31, 2000.
    "Fit To Be Tried" by Georges Feydeau VC VII.10.3 (Cast: Chris Lacey, Mary Beth Spore, Rick Sparks, Joe Szurek, Beth Tiedemann, Marilyn Jensen, Brandi Darr; Directed by Joanne Viano with Assoc. Director, Larry Whatule); "Dentity Crisis" by Christopher Durang (Cast: Sheila Confer, Michelle Tracey, Bill Pamerleau playing four characters, Mark McColloch, Shirley Mileca). Mar. 22, 23, 2001. (For photos of cast, "Fit To Be Tried", see UPG.RG.60 Visual Images--Prints--UPG Players-- "Fit To Be Tried"--Cast.)
    - Performing Arts, April 6-8, 1979 - April 1-3, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 4, Shelf 5, Shelf 6)
  - Talks, Lectures, Speeches, September 23, 1992 - October 11, 2006; 8.
    Apt, Dr. Jay. "This View of Earth", a slide show from outer space, presented Sept. 7, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater by Dr. Jay Apt, a former astronaut. VC VIII.4 Dr. Apt flew as a member of the crew of the Space Shuttle Atlantis (1991), was Endeavor's flight engineer (1992), flew again aboard Endeavor (1994) and served aboard Atlantis as it docked with the Russian Mir space station (1996). Program sponsored by the Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village. Arthur St. Clair Lectureship 2000, Oct. 19 (1st lecture)
    Hinderaker, Dr. Eric A. "Westmoreland County and the Struggle for Europe in the Ohio Country", first in the annual [Arthur] St. Clair Lecture Series, Thursday Oct. 19, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VIII.7.a Dr. Hinderaker is an Assoc. Prof. of History at the Univ. Of Utah and a distinguished French and Indian War Scholar. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files, Ser.: [Arthur St]. Clair Lectureship. 2001, Oct. 18 (2nd)
    Calloway, Dr. Collin Gordon. "The Role of the Native Americans at the Time of the Revolution in the West", 2nd in the annual Arthur St. Clair Lecture Series, Oct. 18, 2001, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VIII.7.b Dr. Calloway is the Chair of the Dept. of Native American Studies, Dartmouth College. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files, Ser.: [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    2002, Oct. 17 (3rd) Majewski, Dr. John "Thomas Jefferson's Economic Revolution from Below." 3rd in the annual Arthur St. Clair Lecture Series. Oct. 17, 2002. Ferguson Theatre. VC VIII.7.c Dr. Majewski is an Assoc. Prof. of History at the University of California Santa Barbara. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files, Ser.: [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    2003, Oct. 16 (4th) Warren, Dr. Kenneth "A Keystone of America's Industrial Greatness: the Coke Industry of the Connellsville Area." 4th in the annual Arthur St. Clair Lecture Series. Oct. 16, 2003. Ferguson Theater. VC VIII.7.d Dr. Kenneth Warren is Emeritus Fellow of Jesus College, Oxford University. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files, Ser.: [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    2005, Oct. 12 (6th) Anderson, Dr. Fred "Why the French and Indian War is Worth Remembering", the 6th annual St. Clair Lecture, October 12, 2005. Ferguson Theater, UPG. VC VIII.7.e Dr. Fred Anderson is Professor of History, University of Colorado at Boulder. Sponsored by Westmoreland Heritage, the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg and The Westmoreland County Historical Society. See also, UPG.RG.52 Subject Files, Ser. [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    2006, Oct. 11 (7th) Tokar, Dr. Franklin K. "A Magnet for Good Architecture: The Laurel Hill Highlands from Mason House to Fallingwater, and Beyond." 7th annual Arthur St. Clair Lectureship, Oct. 11, 2006, Ferguson Theater. Dr. Franklin K. Tokar is a professor in the History of Art and Architecture Department at the Univ. of Pittsburgh, Oakland Campus. For a DVD of this Lecture, SEE: UPG.RG.60.DVD.3. See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Arthur St. Clair Lectureship.
    Bortz, Dr. William M. Lecture entitled, "Creating A Meaningful Third Age: Dare To Be 100!", by the nationally recognized physician and author. April 18, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VIII.5
    Carter, Rubin "Hurricane." Public Lecture, "The Story of the Hurricane: Justice and the Legal System". Feb. 10, 2000, Chambers Hall Gymnasium. VC VIII.8 See Also: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files--Events (Campus Sponsored)--Black History Month, Feb, 2000, for autographed programs, news clippings. UPG.RG.60 Visual Images. Ser.: Prints – Carter, Rubin "Hurricane"
    Clark, Joe. Educator who transformed the formerly raucous Eastside High in New Jersey into a model school. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, February 28, 1995. VC VIII.1 Educator who transformed the formerly raucous Eastside High in New Jersey into a model school. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, February 28, 1995. Sponsored by UPG Activities Board in cooperation with the Organization for Black Awareness and the Greensburg/Jeannette NAACP branch. (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27, news release, February 13, 1995.)
    Clark, Ramsey. (See UPG.RG.60 Video Cassettes IV Forums, Symposia, Seminars, Workshops: Criminal Justice Day, March 25, 1993.)
    Cobetto Lecture Series. 2006, Feb. 23. "How to be Good" presented by Randy Cohen, Columnist, New York Times. VC VIII.19
    Cultura, La. 2002. The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci. Lecture: Farago, Dr. Claire, Univ. of Colorado. VC VIII.15 "Leonardo da Vinci, Cultural Hero: Is His Legacy Scientific Legacy Fact or Fiction?" Jan. 31, 2002.
    Culture, La. 2003. A Paris. Lectures: VC VIII.16.A Collins, Dr. Bradford,Univ. of South Carolina. "Impressionism: Manet, Monet and Urbanism." Jan. 23, 2003. VC VIII.16.B Lloyd, Dr. Rosemary, Indiana University. "Baudelaire, Mallarme and the Modern City." Jan. 27, 2003. VC VIII.16.C Muller, Dr. Edward, Univ. of Pittsburgh. "Creating the New Paris in the Late 19th Century." Jan. 30, 2003.
    Cultura, La. 2004. Spain: Collins, Dr. Bradford,Univ. of South Carolina. VC VIII.17.A. Treasuries and Legacy of the Golden Age. Lectures: Toker, Dr. Franklin, University of Pittsburgh. "Velazquez's "Las Meninas." "A Captivating Image and Its Cruel Reality", Jan. 20, 2004. VC VIII.17.B Guilmartin, Dr. John, Ohio State University. "The Battle of Lepanto: How Spanish Naval Technology Changed the Course of Empires", Jan. 22, 2004. VC VIII.17.C Beverley, Dr. John, University of Pittsburgh. "Don Quixote and Us: Reflections on Empire, Past and Present", Jan. 29, 2004.
    Cultura, La. 2006. Classical Greece: Tradition and Challenge. Lectures: VC VIII.18A "Classical Greek Influences in the Modern World." Oct. 27, 2005. VC VIII.18B Weis, Dr. Anne, Prof. of History of Art & Architecture, Univ. of Pittsburgh, "Encounters with the Divine in Greece and the Hellenistic World." Jan. 19, 2006. VC VIII.18C Pamerleau, Dr. William, Assoc. Prof. of Philosophy, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, "Socrates' Ethical Challenge", Feb. 16, 2006. VC VIII.18D Orange, Dr. Walter, Assistant Prof. of Mathematics, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. "Searching for Pythagoras", Mar. 22, 2006. N.B. For La Cultura Lecture Series from 2007-to date, See: UPG.RG.60.DVD.6.A-
    Elana Castro, Maria Elena. Cuban journalist, short story writer and poet reads and discusses her works. VC VIII.9 She served as a journalist during the Cuban Revolution, a foreign correspondent in China, news editor and journalism professor in Angola and as a literary, art, movie critic, Script writer for radio and television. April 19, 2001. UPG Village Hall. See Also: UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases, 4/9/01.
    Grossman, Lt. Col. Dave. "Are We Killing Our Kids" by former U.S. Army Ranger and West Point psychology professor. Monday, Oct. 14, 2002, UPG Ferguson Theater. VC VIII.14 See also: RG 27 Ser.: News Releases 10/7/02; UPG.RG.55 News Clippings, 10/17/02.
    Madres, Las, de la Plaza de Mayo (Mothers of May Square). April 17, 2001, UPG Village Hall. VC VIII.1 [organization which staged peaceful marches in the Plaze de Mayo in Buenos Aires to demand justice and information about their children who "disappeared" during the 1970's and 1980's under the oppressive military government at that time. For news releases, see UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases 4/09/02.]
    Matta, Pedro Alejandro. VC VIII.13 "Confronting the Past: A Walk Through a Twentieth Century Torture Center; Villa Grimaldi, Santiago, Chile" by Pedro Alejandro Matta, a survivor of the Chilean Military Junta torture camp in the 1970's. Tuesday, October 1, 2002, 7:30 p.m., UPG Ferguson Theater. See also: UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases, 9/16/02.
    Mathis, Judge Greg. VC VIII.10 Public Lecture, "Overcoming Life's Challenge". Monday, Feb. 4, 2002, Chambers Hall Gymnasium. Part of Black History Month, 2002. See also: UPG.RG.27 Ser.: News Releases. News Release 1/22/02, "Television Judge at UPG". RG52 Subject Files. Ser.: Events (Campus Sponsored)--Black History Month, 2002 UPG.RG.60 Prints–Mathis, Judge Greg.
    Power, Margaret. "The Politics of Right-Wing Women in Latin America" by Margaret Power of the Illinois Institute of Technology, Monday, Feb. 11, 2002. VC VIII.11 Subject is on the pivotal role rightist women have played in their nations' modern history, including those who marched against President Goulart in Brazil and those who organized against Salvador Allende in Chile. Also examined is what is the U.S. Government's relationship to right-wing women in Latin America. Sponsored by the Behavioral Sciences Academic Village, Humanities Academic Village, Rossetti International House.
    Provost, Dr. George Foster. Professor, English Department, Duquesne University and Director of the Christopher Columbus Project; Research Associate for Columbus Studies, Brown University. VC VIII.3 Topic: "Will the Real Columbus Please Stand Up?"; 6 October 1992, Smith Hall, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg; sponsored by the Pennsylvania Humanities Council; introduction of speaker by Dr. Ruth Kuschmierz. Note: Early portion of tape defective; start tape at counter 1.50, otherwise the tape will stop at either counter reading .42 or 1.44 and will rewind. For UPG news release see RG27 News Releases, September 23, 1992.
    Rosmus, Anna. VC VIII.2 Author, researcher speaks on the hidden Nazi past of Passau, Germany and focuses on wartime atrocities committed under Hitler by people of Passau and is based on what she uncovered as a teenager while writing an essay for a European wide contest. University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, October 20, 1994. (For UPG news release, see UPG.RG.27 news release October 10, 1994.)
    UPG Cultural Series 1999, Sept. 24, 25, 26. "The Second Mrs. Damyan," an original play by K.C. Constantine. (See RG 60 VC VII.7 and UPG.RG.25 Ser.: UPG Cultural Series.) 2000, Oct. 3.
    Halberstam, David. "The Future of Celebrity" a lecture presented as part of the UPG Cultural Series, Oct. 3, 2000, UPG Ferguson Theater by David Halverstam, a Pulitzer Prize winner. VC VIII.6a See also, UPG.RG.25 Library, Ser.: UPG Cultural Series. 2001, Oct. 25.
    Krulwich, Robert. VC VIII.6b "Why Things Are The Way They Are" (with a focus on Science and Technology), Oct. 25, 2001, UPG Ferguson Theater by Robert Krulwich, an ABC News Correspondent. [spoke and answered questions in re the terrorist attack on the World Trade Center on Sept. 11, 2001]. See also UPG.RG.25 Library, Ser.: UPG Cultural Series.
    - Talks, Lectures, Speeches, September 23, 1992 - October 11, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 6, Shelf 7)
  - Class Instruction, Winter 1983 - March 26, 1988; 9.
    Communication. Dr. Donald Egolf, Instructor. 2 cassettes.
    Cassette 1: On generating and evaluating ideas. Topic "How Can We Improve the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg?" VC IX. 1a Class participation. circa, March 26, 1988. 30 minutes
    Cassette 2: Team of four students (3 males, 1 female) whose task is to select two candidates from among a number to share the use of a kidney machine. VC IX. 1b Evaluation and selection of the two candidates are to be made on the potential contributions of the individuals to society. The task is to include a report with recommendation of two candidates with a rationale for selection. circa, 44 minutes.
    German skits. 2 skits. January, 1986. circa 7 minutes. VC IX. 2
    Spanish skits. 4 skits. Winter, 1983. circa 20 minutes. Nancy Estrada, Instructor. VC IX. 3
    Dissection of a cow's eye. [undtd] VC IX. 4
    Commercials for UPG. [Dr. L. Beeson's Persuasion Class. Fall 1986]. VC IX. 5
    - Class Instruction, Winter 1983 - March 26, 1988 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 7)
  - Miscellaneous, June 14, 1992 - January 16, 2005; 10.
    Greensburg Croquet Club, June 14, 1992. VC X. 1
    Semester at Sea, University of Pittsburgh. 17 minutes. VC X. 2 A video by Martin Darrah and Katrina Greene. An IFV/ISE [Institute for Shipboard Education] Production. 2 copies.
    60 Minutes--Clip from the 60 Minutes TV broadcast of 1/16/05, "The Insider". VC X.3 [2 second clip of UPG students attending a talk by Jeffrey Wigand, former tobacco industry executive on 11/18/04 in the Ferguson Theater. For a preview article on the upcoming event, see The [UPG] Insider, 11/18/04, p 1-2, "'Insider to Inform UPG Today'"]
    - Miscellaneous, June 14, 1992 - January 16, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 7)